[Lee Hyesung]
[I'm home, where are you?]
[I'm at a gym]
[Do you mind having
dinner with me?]
You're
late today, sir
Are you following me?
It's my routine
You haven't even
come here recently
You know a lot about me
Let me ask something
When will you let
Hyesung go?
Why should I do that?
I told you the ones
he liked were all trash
Among them
you're the worst
I couldn't even dare
to touch him
Yet you use him, saying
you'll make him famous?
Hey
my feelings
for Hyesung is real
Hey, come on!
I can just get in
like it's a coincidence
No, you shouldn't
If Shin Yoo-il
is really in there
I'll cancel everything
you owed me
Are you kidding me?
Soobin, you know
we've met before
When Hyesung was
trapped in a warehouse
remember that kid who
stayed there with him?
That was me
It was since then
that this city boy
became my idol
What? Is that all?
I expected
something epic
But Hyesung thinks
it was you who was there
Have you been
lying to him
only to stay next to him?
That's disgusting
isn't it?
You've pretended
to be his good friend
deceiving him
for over ten years